Guide to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association records, circa 1800-2022 MS2027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administration files, 1828-2010; MS2027 Series 2
  - Board of Directors files: Correspondence, First vice president position, 1990 August 09 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Board of Directors files: Memorandum, Financial statements, 1990 January 11 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Board of Directors files: Memorandum, Meeting schedules, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Board of Directors files: Memorandums, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Board of Directors files: Memorandums, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors files: Report, President Bruce Wood to the Board, 1985 November 09 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Board of Directors files: Report, "Some Dark Clouds Ahead," by William Davies, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Board of Directors files: Report, "Proposal to Publish Occasional Papers" by Dave Johnson, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1975 December 31 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Advisory Committee, US waters permit, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Advisory Committee, Nomination-Constance Morella, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Advisory Committee, Widewater Ramp, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Advisory Committee, Nomination-Nancy Long, 1976-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Advisory Committee, Nomination-Ken Rollins, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Member Lists, Advisory Committee, 1977-1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1981 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Agenda, Advisory Committee, 1981 December 03 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Agenda, Advisory Committee, 1982 December 04 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1983 March 05 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Agenda, Advisory Committee, 1983 December 03 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Advisory Committee, Whitehurst Freeway, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Resolution, Advisory Committee, Resource management, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Agenda, Advisory Committee, 1984 December 01 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Agenda, Advisory Committee, 1986 February 08 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Advisory Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1991 December 01 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1992 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1992 June 13 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1992 September 19 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Agenda, Advisory Committee, 1992 December 12 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Charter, Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1993 January 23 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1993 April 03 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1993 June 12 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1993 September 11 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1993 December 11 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Report, Advisory Committee, Committee justification, Circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Agenda, Advisory Committee, 1994 March 12 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Advisory Committee, 1996 December 14 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Notes, Advisory Committee, 12/12, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Archives Committee, Naming of collection, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Archives Committee, Search for repository, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Archives Committee, Appointees, 1989-1993 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Notes, Archives Committee, Status of archives, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Report, Archives Committee, Status of archives, 1989 June 25 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Report, Archives Committee, Location suggestions, 1989 September 24 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Archives Committee, Donations, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Budget Committee, Estimates, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Budget Committee, Operating meeting, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Report, Canal Improvement Committee, Recommendations, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Executive Committee, 1989 August 17 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Executive Committee, 1990 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Executive Committee, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Report, Flood Control Policy Committee, Dickerson Resource Recovery Facility, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Report, Internal Audit Committee, Financial status, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum. Legal Advisory Committee, Appointee Jack Stickles, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Lodging Committee, Membership, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Ballots, Nomination Committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Nomination Committee, Candidate information, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: List, Nomination Committee, Nominees, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Nomination Committee, Anne Murphy, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Guidelines, Nomination Committee, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: List, Nomination Committee, Members, 1985-1993 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: List, Nomination Committee, Nominees, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Report, Nomination Committee, Nominees, 1989 December 03 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Guidelines, Nomination Committee, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Nomination Committee, Appointees, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Nomination Committee, New members, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting Notes, Nomination Committee, 1991 November 19 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Nomination Committee, Incumbent board members, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Nomination Committee, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Guidelines, Nomination Committee, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Nomination Committee, Nominees, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Nomination Committee, Nominating process, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Nomination Committee, Chairman John Fondersmith, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Nomination Committee, Election results, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Nomination Committee, Nomination notification, nd, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Meeting, Program & Policy Committee, 1960 December 22 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Correspondence, Programs Committee, Appointee Jack Francis, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Programs Committee, Appointee John Frye, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Programs Committee, Heritage Hike, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Programs Committee, Heritage Hike, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Publications Committee, Lodging Guide, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Committee files: Meeting material: Memorandum, Western Maryland Railway Trail Committee, Representation, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Committee files: Commissions: Meeting, Canal Advisory Commission, 1991 March 09 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Committee files: Commissions: Publication, "Healing a River-The Potomac-1940-1990", Interstate Commission on Potomac River Basin (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Committee files: Commissions: Meeting, National Historical Park Advisory Commission, 1991 June 15 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Committee files: Commissions: Meeting, National Historical Park Advisory Commission, 1991 September 14 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Committee files: Commissions: Meeting Agenda, National Historical Park Advisory Commission, 1991 December 07 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Committee files: Commissions: Correspondence, National Historical Park Advisory Commission, Allegany County, Circa 1991 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Committee files: Commissions: Correspondence, Potomac River Basin Consortium, Representative, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Committee files: Conferences: Correspondence, International Conference on Historic Canals, Speakers, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Committee files: Conferences: List, International Conference on Historic Canals, Participants, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Committee member lists: List, Members, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Committee member lists: List, Volunteers, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Committee member lists: List, Members, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Committee member lists: List, Members, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Committee reports and memos [1/2], 2005; Series 2 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Committee reports and memos [2/2], 2005; Series 2 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Financial files: Budgets: Report, Estimate-archives, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Financial files: Budgets: Report, Balance sheet, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Financial files: Budgets: Report, Budget justification summary-FY 1994/1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Financial files: Budgets: Memorandum, Budget review, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Financial files: Correspondence, Treasurer Bill Evans, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Financial files: Memorandum, Treasurer Bill Evans, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Financial files: Memorandum, Treasurer Bill Evans, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Financial files: Memorandum, Treasurer Bill Evans, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1977 April (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1978 April (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1978 July (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1983 January 12 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Financial files: Report, Budget proposal, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1984 December (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Financial files: Report, Budget proposal, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1986 January 12 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1987 January 09 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1989 September (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1990 June (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Financial files: Annual Report, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Financial files: Report, Executive budget summary, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Financial files: Report, Treasurer, 1994 March (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Financial files: Report, Contributions, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Financial files: Report, Contributions, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Financial files: Report, Contributions, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Financial files: Report, Canal projects, nd, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Financial files: Report, 5 year development cost, nd, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Financial files: Receipt, Rent of canal grounds, 1930 July 01 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Financial files: Treasurer's correspondence secretary's copies, 2000; Series 2 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Financial files: 2000 thru 2002, 2000-2002; Series 2 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Legal files: Agreements, Georgetown agreement with adjacent landowner, 1969-1980 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Legal files: Agreement, Offer to sell real property-vendor, Circa 1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Legal files: Agreement, Adopt-A-Park -- Conococheaque Sportsman Club, Circa 1983 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Legal files: By-laws, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Legal files: By-laws, amendment, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Legal files: By-laws, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Legal files: By-laws, amendments, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Legal files: By-laws, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Legal files: By-laws, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Legal files: By-laws, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Legal files: By-laws, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Legal files: By-laws, proposed, nd, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Legal files: By-laws, amendments, nd, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Legal files: By-laws, amendments -- article II, nd, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Legal files: Certificate of incorporation, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Legal files: Certificate of incorporation: amended, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Legal files: Certificate of incorporation: amended, nd, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Legal files: Correspondence, Lawyer fees-Ed Wesley, 1976 December 12 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Legal files: Issue, Suit against Corps of Engineers -- Construction permit, 1975 May (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Legal files: Issue, Proposal to water canal -- Advanced Waste Treatment, 1975 May (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Legal files: Issue, Suit dismissal -- Howard H. Callaway, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Legal files: Issue, Bill HR 11226 - To dedicate Chesapeake & Ohio Canal to Justice William Douglas, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Bill H.R. 11226, 1975 December 17; Item 1
  - Legal files: Issue, Potomac River Historical Area, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Legal files: Issue, Bill HR 861 -- National Trails System Act, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Legal files: Issue, Wiley Ford Bridge, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Legal files: Issue, Injunction against MD state highway administration over bridge over Potomac at Wiley Ford, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Legal files: Issue, Commercial advertising in Rock Creek Park Tennis Center, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Legal files: Statement, Policy statement, 1970 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Legal files: Statement, Potomac River Historical Area Act of 1975, by James B. Coulter, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Legal files: Davies Legal Fund material: Correspondence, contributors, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Legal files: Davies Legal Fund material: Correspondence, contributors, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Legal files: Davies Legal Fund material: Correspondence, contributors, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Legal files: Davies Legal Fund material: Correspondence, contributors, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Legal files: Davies Legal Fund material: Correspondence, contributors, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Administration files: Directory, Emergency staff, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Administration files: Directory, National Historical Park personnel, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Administration files: Directory, National Historical Park personnel, 1989 April (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Administration files: Directory, National Historical Park employees, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Administration files: Directory, Visitor Information, Spring/Summer, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Administration files: Directory, List of Association lawyers and attorneys, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Administration files: Directory, District locations, nd, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Administration files: Organizational charts: Chart, National Historical Park staff, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Administration files: Organizational charts: Chart, National Historical Park staff, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Administration files: Organizational charts: Chart, Executive committee, nd, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Administration files: Schedule, Canal Clipper barge, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Administration files: Schedule, Calendar of Events, 1982-1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Administration files: Schedule, Annual duties, nd, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Administration files: Procedures: Floor plans, Georgetown National Historical Park Visitors Center, nd, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Administration files: Procedures: Guidelines, Park rules on biking, camping and vehicles, nd, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Administration files: Procedures: Letterhead, assorted Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association letterhead and envelopes, nd, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association logo, undated; Item 1
  - Administration files: Procedures: Logos, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Company, nd, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Administration files: Procedures: Postings, Information Officer, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Administration files: Procedures: Summary, Visitor facilities, nd, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, Canal property preservation, Justice William Douglas, 1954 April 22 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, Canal property preservation, Justice William Douglas, 1954 May 04 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Historical Park, 1957 February 13 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, George Washington Memorial Parkway, 1957 May 31 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, Proclamation-Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Monument, 1961 January 18 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Historical Park, 1969 December 01 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Historical Park, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Administration files: Memorandum, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Administration files: Memorandum, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Administration files: Memorandum, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Administration files: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Administration files: Memorandum, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Administration files: Report, The Chesapeake & Ohio Canal and the Antebellum Commerce of Old Georgetown, by Rogers W. Young, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Administration files: Report, Outline Program for the Use & Enjoyment of the Potomac Valley, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Administration files: Report, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Tunnel Area-Interpretive Guide, by William Davies, Circa 1959 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Administration files: Report, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Park, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Administration files: Report, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Environmental Assessment-General Plan, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Administration files: Report, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Historical Park-General Plan, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Administration files: Report, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Historical Park-Development Concept Plan, Circa 1976 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Administration files: Reports, Record of Decision, Environmental Assessment for the Development Concept Plan for Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Historical Park, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Administration files: Report, Record of Decision and Finding of No Significant Impact-Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Historical Park, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Administration files: Report, Restoration of George Washington Canal, Great Falls, VA, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Administration files: Report, Mark Up Statement for Management of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Historical Park, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Administration files: Report, Canal Towpath Updates, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Administration files: Report, Toward a Premier National Park System-The Wilderness Society, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Administration files: Report, Rails to Trails-Railroad Rights of Way and Their Potential for Conversion to Multi-use Trails, Maryland Department of Natural Resources, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Administration files: Report, Briefing Statement-Capitol Crescent Trail, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement for Management, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Administration files: Report, Regional Trail Corridor Study for the Mid-Atlantic States, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Administration files: Report, The Vail Agenda, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Administration files: Report, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-The Making of a Park, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Administration files: Report, Briefing Statements-Dam 4 & 5/Rewatering Chesapeake & Ohio Canal/Olmsted Island Footbridges/Georgetown Visitor Center, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Administration files: Report, Williamsport Preservation Training Center-Weekly Field Report, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Administration files: Report, Work Projects, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Administration files: Report, Survey-National Park Friends Groups-National Park Foundation, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Administration files: Report, Strategic Plan-National Park Trust, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Administration files: Report, Resources Management Plan, Circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Administration files: Report, Service-wide Line Item Construction and Harper's Ferry-Major Rehab Priorities, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement-Reconstruction of Towpath at Big Slackwater, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement-Stabilization of Towpath at Widewater, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement-Engineering Studies & Historic Structure Report for Stabilization of the Conococheaque & Tonoloway Aqueducts, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement-Conversion of Historic Structures at Williamsport to Major Visitor Use, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement-Monocacy Aqueduct Restoration, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement-Safety Repairs to Dams, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement-Francis Scott Key Memorial and Park, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Administration files: Report, Statement-Georgetown Visitor Center, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 27)